Office of the Registrar, School of Medicine Records UA075
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Grade files, 1973 -- 2013; UA075.003; 13.2 Linear Feet
  - Cardiovascular System Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00046 (Box 93)
  - Endocrine System Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00047 (Box 93)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00048 (Box 93)
  - Musculo-skeletal System Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00049 (Box 93)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00050 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00051 (Box 93)
  - Respiratory System Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00052 (Box 93)
  - Psychiatry Second Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00053 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Misc First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00054 (Box 93)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00055 (Box 93)
  - Behavioral Science Part I and Primary Care First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00056 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00057 (Box 93)
  - Cell Biology - Memo First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00058 (Box 93)
  - General Pathology First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00059 (Box 93)
  - Hematology First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00060 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00061 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00062 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiologoy Final Exam First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00063 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology and Advanced First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00064 (Box 93)
  - Neuropharmacology First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00065 (Box 93)
  - Neurosciences First Year, 1977 -- 1978; UA075.003.093.00066 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Correspondence Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00067 (Box 93)
  - Cardiovascular System Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00068 (Box 93)
  - Endocrinology Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00069 (Box 93)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00070 (Box 93)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00071 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00072 (Box 93)
  - Respiratory System Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00073 (Box 93)
  - Psychiatry Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00074 (Box 93)
  - Muscolo-skeletal System Second Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00075 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Correspondence First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00076 (Box 93)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00077 (Box 93)
  - Behavioral Science & Primary Care First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00078 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00079 (Box 93)
  - Cell Differentiation First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00080 (Box 93)
  - General Pathology First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00081 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00082 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00083 (Box 93)
  - Infectious Disease First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00084 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00085 (Box 93)
  - Neuropharmacology First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00086 (Box 93)
  - Neurosciences First Year, 1978 -- 1979; UA075.003.093.00087 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Correspondence Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00088 (Box 93)
  - Cardiovascular System Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00089 (Box 93)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00090 (Box 93)
  - Endocrine-Metabolic Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00091 (Box 93)
  - G.I. Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00092 (Box 93)
  - Infectious Disease/Parasitology Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00093 (Box 93)
  - Musculo-skeletal System Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00094 (Box 93)
  - Pharmacology Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00095 (Box 93)
  - Renal Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00096 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive System Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00097 (Box 93)
  - Psychiatry Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00098 (Box 93)
  - Pulmonary Second Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00099 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Correspondence First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00100 (Box 93)
  - Gross Anatomy First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00101 (Box 93)
  - Behav. Sci. & Prim. Care I First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00102 (Box 93)
  - Behav. Sci. & Prim. Care II First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00103 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00104 (Box 93)
  - General Pathology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00105 (Box 93)
  - Hematology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00106 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00107 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00108 (Box 93)
  - Infectious Disease/Parasitology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00109 (Box 93)
  - Issues in Comm. Health First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00110 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00111 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00112 (Box 93)
  - Pharmacology First Year, 1979 -- 1980; UA075.003.093.00113 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Correspondence Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00114 (Box 93)
  - Cardiovascular System Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00115 (Box 93)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00116 (Box 93)
  - Endocrine Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00117 (Box 93)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00118 (Box 93)
  - Musculo-Skeletal Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00119 (Box 93)
  - Physical Diagnosis Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00120 (Box 93)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00121 (Box 93)
  - Renal Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00122 (Box 93)
  - Psychiatry Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00123 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00124 (Box 93)
  - Respiratory Second Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00125 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Correspondence First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00126 (Box 93)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00127 (Box 93)
  - Behav. Sci. & Prim. Care I, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00128 (Box 93)
  - Behav. Sci. & Prim. Care II First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00129 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00130 (Box 93)
  - Epidemiology & Biostat First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00131 (Box 93)
  - General Pathology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00132 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00133 (Box 93)
  - Hematology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00134 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00135 (Box 93)
  - Infectious Disease/Parasitology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00136 (Box 93)
  - Issues in Comm. Health First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00137 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00138 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00139 (Box 93)
  - Prin. of Physiology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00140 (Box 93)
  - Pharmacology First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00141 (Box 93)
  - Selectives First Year, 1980 -- 1981; UA075.003.093.00142 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Corres. Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00143 (Box 93)
  - Cardiovascular Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00144 (Box 93)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00145 (Box 93)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00146 (Box 93)
  - Intro to Med & Surgery Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00147 (Box 93)
  - Endocrine System Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00148 (Box 93)
  - Musculo-Skeletal Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00149 (Box 93)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00150 (Box 93)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00151 (Box 93)
  - Pulmonary Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00152 (Box 93)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00153 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive System Second Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00154 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Corres. First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00155 (Box 93)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00156 (Box 93)
  - BSPC - Human Development First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00157 (Box 93)
  - BSPC - Interviewing First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00158 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00159 (Box 93)
  - Epiidemiology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00160 (Box 93)
  - Hematology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00161 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00162 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00163 (Box 93)
  - Issues in Comm. Health First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00164 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00165 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00166 (Box 93)
  - Pathology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00167 (Box 93)
  - Pharmacology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00168 (Box 93)
  - Physiology First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00169 (Box 93)
  - Selectives First Year, 1981 -- 1982; UA075.003.093.00170 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Corres. Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00171 (Box 93)
  - Cardiovascular Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00172 (Box 93)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00173 (Box 93)
  - Endocrine System Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00174 (Box 93)
  - G.I. (Gastroenterology) Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00175 (Box 93)
  - Intro to Med & Surgery Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00176 (Box 93)
  - Musculo-Skeletal Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00177 (Box 93)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00178 (Box 93)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00179 (Box 93)
  - Pulmonary Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00180 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive System Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00181 (Box 93)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00182 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Corres. First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00183 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Corres. Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00184 (Box 93)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00185 (Box 93)
  - Behavioral Science I First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00186 (Box 93)
  - Behavioral Science II First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00187 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00188 (Box 93)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00189 (Box 93)
  - Pathology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00190 (Box 93)
  - Hematology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00191 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00192 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00193 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology I First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00194 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology II First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00195 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00196 (Box 93)
  - Pharmacology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00197 (Box 93)
  - Physiology First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00198 (Box 93)
  - Selectives First Year, 1982 -- 1983; UA075.003.093.00199 (Box 93)
  - Cardiovascular Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00200 (Box 93)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00201 (Box 93)
  - Endocrine System Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00202 (Box 93)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00203 (Box 93)
  - Intro to Med & Surgery Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00204 (Box 93)
  - Musculo Skeletal Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00205 (Box 93)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00206 (Box 93)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00207 (Box 93)
  - Pulmonary Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00208 (Box 93)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00209 (Box 93)
  - Reproductive System Second Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00210 (Box 93)
  - Grade Worksheet/Corres. First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00211 (Box 93)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00212 (Box 93)
  - Behavioral Science I First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00213 (Box 93)
  - Behavioral Science II First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00214 (Box 93)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00215 (Box 93)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00216 (Box 93)
  - Hematology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00217 (Box 93)
  - Histology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00218 (Box 93)
  - Immunology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00219 (Box 93)
  - Issues in Comm. Health First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00220 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology I First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00221 (Box 93)
  - Medical Microbiology II First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00222 (Box 93)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00223 (Box 93)
  - Pathology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00224 (Box 93)
  - Pharmacology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00225 (Box 93)
  - Physiology First Year, 1983 -- 1984; UA075.003.093.00226 (Box 93)
  - Northeastern Sch. Of Pharmacology, 1983 -- 1990; UA075.003.095.00001 (Box 95)
  - Miscellaneous Grade Info., 1977 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00002 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00003 (Box 95)
  - Cardiovascular Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00004 (Box 95)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00005 (Box 95)
  - Endocrine System Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00006 (Box 95)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00007 (Box 95)
  - Intro to Med & Surg Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00008 (Box 95)
  - Musculoskeletal Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00009 (Box 95)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00010 (Box 95)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00011 (Box 95)
  - Pulmonary Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00012 (Box 95)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00013 (Box 95)
  - Reproductive System Second Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00014 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00015 (Box 95)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00016 (Box 95)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00017 (Box 95)
  - BSPC-Interviewing First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00018 (Box 95)
  - BSPC-Human Development First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00019 (Box 95)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00020 (Box 95)
  - Hematology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00021 (Box 95)
  - Histology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00022 (Box 95)
  - Human Nutrition First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00023 (Box 95)
  - Immunology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00024 (Box 95)
  - Issues in Comm. Hlth. First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00025 (Box 95)
  - Med. Microbiology I First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00026 (Box 95)
  - Med. Microbiology II First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00027 (Box 95)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00028 (Box 95)
  - Pathology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00029 (Box 95)
  - Pharmacology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00030 (Box 95)
  - Physiology First Year, 1984 -- 1985; UA075.003.095.00031 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00032 (Box 95)
  - Cardiovascular Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00033 (Box 95)
  - Dermatology Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00034 (Box 95)
  - Endocrinology Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00035 (Box 95)
  - Gastroenterology Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00036 (Box 95)
  - Intro to Med & Surg Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00037 (Box 95)
  - Musculoskeletal Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00038 (Box 95)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00039 (Box 95)
  - Pulmonary Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00040 (Box 95)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00041 (Box 95)
  - Renal System Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00042 (Box 95)
  - Reproductive System Second Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00043 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00044 (Box 95)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00045 (Box 95)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00046 (Box 95)
  - Cases Program First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00047 (Box 95)
  - Cell Biology First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00048 (Box 95)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00049 (Box 95)
  - Hematology First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00050 (Box 95)
  - Histology First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00051 (Box 95)
  - Human Growth & Devel. First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00052 (Box 95)
  - Immunology First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00053 (Box 95)
  - Interviewing First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00054 (Box 95)
  - Issues in Comm. Hlth. First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00055 (Box 95)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00056 (Box 95)
  - Physiology First Year, 1985 -- 1986; UA075.003.095.00057 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00058 (Box 95)
  - Family Medicine Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00059 (Box 95)
  - Intro to Med & Surg Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00060 (Box 95)
  - Microbiology Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00061 (Box 95)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00062 (Box 95)
  - Pathology Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00063 (Box 95)
  - Pathophysiology Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00064 (Box 95)
  - Pharmacology Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00065 (Box 95)
  - Problem Based Learning Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00066 (Box 95)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00067 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00068 (Box 95)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00069 (Box 95)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00070 (Box 95)
  - C.D.T. Biology First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00071 (Box 95)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00072 (Box 95)
  - Growth & Development First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00073 (Box 95)
  - Hematology First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00074 (Box 95)
  - Histology First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00075 (Box 95)
  - Immunology First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00076 (Box 95)
  - Interviewing First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00077 (Box 95)
  - Issues in Comm. Hlth. First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00078 (Box 95)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00079 (Box 95)
  - Physiology First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00080 (Box 95)
  - Problem Based Learning First Year, 1986 -- 1987; UA075.003.095.00081 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00082 (Box 95)
  - General Pathology Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00083 (Box 95)
  - Intro to Med & Surg Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00084 (Box 95)
  - Microbiology Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00085 (Box 95)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00086 (Box 95)
  - Nutrition Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00087 (Box 95)
  - Pharmacology Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00088 (Box 95)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00089 (Box 95)
  - Pathophysiology Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00090 (Box 95)
  - Systemic Pathology Second Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00091 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00092 (Box 95)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00093 (Box 95)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00094 (Box 95)
  - C.D.T. Biology First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00095 (Box 95)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00096 (Box 95)
  - Family Medicine First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00097 (Box 95)
  - Growth & Development First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00098 (Box 95)
  - Hematology First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00099 (Box 95)
  - Histology First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00100 (Box 95)
  - History of Medicine First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00101 (Box 95)
  - Immunology First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00102 (Box 95)
  - Interviewing First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00103 (Box 95)
  - Issues in Comm. Hlth. First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00104 (Box 95)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00105 (Box 95)
  - Physiology First Year, 1987 -- 1988; UA075.003.095.00106 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00107 (Box 95)
  - General Pathology Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00108 (Box 95)
  - Microbiology Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00109 (Box 95)
  - Neuroscience Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00110 (Box 95)
  - Nutrition Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00111 (Box 95)
  - Pathophysiology Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00112 (Box 95)
  - Pharmacology Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00113 (Box 95)
  - Physical Diagnosis Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00114 (Box 95)
  - Problem Based Learning Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00115 (Box 95)
  - Psychopathology Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00116 (Box 95)
  - Systemic Pathology Second Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00117 (Box 95)
  - Grade Worksheet First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00118 (Box 95)
  - Anatomy First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00119 (Box 95)
  - Biochemistry First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00120 (Box 95)
  - C.D.T. Biology First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00121 (Box 95)
  - Epidemiology Biostats First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00122 (Box 95)
  - Family Medicine First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00123 (Box 95)
  - Growth & Development First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00124 (Box 95)
  - Hematology First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00125 (Box 95)
  - Histology First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00126 (Box 95)
  - History of Medicine First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00127 (Box 95)
  - Immunology First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00128 (Box 95)
  - Interviewing First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00129 (Box 95)
  - Issues in Comm. Hlth. First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00130 (Box 95)
  - Molecular Biology First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00131 (Box 95)
  - Physiology First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00132 (Box 95)
  - Problem Based Learning First Year, 1988 -- 1989; UA075.003.095.00133 (Box 95)